Why join IC Lord? It
is such a big brand, such a wonderful number one
private general insurance company and the
work done here is very good and excellent and how can you also make a name for yourself in it,
how can you also do good earning and good working in it, you will get to
understand everything in detail here.
Within a short time, this policy is being sold on a very large scale.
People are appreciating it in a very wonderful way. The
company has launched an amazing product in
which unlimited sum assured is given,
unlimited re is given, unlimited no
claim bonus is given and A B CD option is
given. Any chronic disease is covered within 30 days.
B BP, sugar, asthma
is covered after 30 days only. You will not get such unique
features in any other company in the market. The
premium
is reasonable. The company
provides excellent handling. The company provides 100% digital platform.
Knowledge training is
available here at a world class level. [
Music]
[Praise]
Hello friends, today we are going to talk about
Why become a health insurance agent of ICC Lombard, how to become one, what are the
benefits of becoming one, how can you join it in part-time working,
how can you join in full-time working,
what is the joining process and why is this company so good, so
great that working for it can be
a passion for you, it can be a
great job for you and how and why
learning work here can be done in a completely digital platform, I am going to
explain all these details of working here,
my name is Yogendra Verma, I am a health
insurance expert and my work is to
recruit agents at ICC Lombard, I
am the recruitment manager here and I
help people generally, I
help them completely in providing a good and excellent platform, friends, those who have
come to the channel for the first time, you have to subscribe to the channel,
share it, comment,
definitely click the bell icon, only then
this working will be very amazing
and great for you, you will keep getting all the latest and
good features, you will keep getting new
videos, you will keep getting information
from subscribing to the channel, so let's talk about
why you got associated with ICC Lombard, it is such a
big brand, so wonderful.  It is the number one
private general insurance company and the
work done here is very good and excellent. How can you also make a name for yourself in it, how can
you also do good
earning and good working in it, you will get to
understand everything in detail here.
This video will hardly be 5 to 7 minutes long,
but for that you will get very valuable inputs,
each and every thing can be useful for you.
So without delay, let's quickly
understand
why to join ICC Lombard and
why to join the health insurance industry. This
industry is so big, so wonderful, how is
it growing and
how big a brand IC Lombard is.
What are its features here, how big is the
strength of the company, you should know this first. So, if
I talk about the company's profile, then the
company generates
WP premium of Rs 2594 crore in a year
and provides PAT of Rs 1919 crore.
PAT is profit after tax. If
you look inside the balance sheet, then the
company generates profit of this much crore in a year
and that's not all.  The
company has issued policies worth Rs 3.62 crore, in which 29
lakh claims have been settled, which is a
very good and excellent
working in itself. The company has 312 branches
and 917 virtual
offices. The suite is very powerful, that is why I
say that all the work in IIC Lord can be
managed digitally and hassle-free. This is
one of the best
software of the company, whose name is IIC Tech Care.
Any customer who
downloads the IIC Care app after taking the policy,
all his policies are visible in the same app. If you want
any doctor consultation, you can get it. If you
need any claim-related support,
you can easily get all the work within that single app.
This IIC Care app
is helpful for agents as well as for customers. It is amazing and
helpful in a very good way,
which has been downloaded by 1.2 crore people till now,
which is tremendous in itself.
This is the power of IIC Lord. Not only this,
talking about the company  So if we
talk about garages, which are your car
garages, where you
can get the vehicles repaired, then 13500
garages are in tie-up with the company. If we
talk about hospitals, then 9500
hospitals are associated with the company and there are
47000 plus doctors, which
is amazing in itself and there are 900 plus internal
surveyors who support and
help you. Plus, if we
talk about the strength of the company, if we talk about IC Lord's multi-channel
distribution setup, then
128000 agents are associated with the company, they are
in good tie-up, they
learn brilliantly and earn well. There
are 300 plus financial institutions. The company has
41 Motor EM partners, 105
digital platforms and 230 affinity
partners, that is, this is the strength
of the company, from which you will understand that IC
Lord is not a small name, it is a very big name, it is a very
big brand, by associating with which there will be
value addition for you. You will
tell people about it.  If you explain that you
come from ICC Lombard, people will
respect you because this company
is number one in settling claims, provides hassle-free and tension-free
treatment services,
keeps its agents under its control,
teaches in a very good manner,
you will find excellent learning and a great environment here.
Friends, ICC Lombard
is the best company. I have told you its profile and
explained to you what
you will get here.
People here join ICC Lombard for health insurance,
join for motor insurance and
join for non-motor insurance.
We are from the health vertical, so our main
focus will be on health insurance and
we do hiring only for health insurance. So, I will talk about explaining
carefully here. The
product here which you will tell the customers, you will
explain it, is an
unmatched product, it gives amazing working, out of which
one of the best
is the latest product named Elevate.
Elevate product is making waves in the market.
Within a short time of one year,
this policy is being sold on a very large scale in a
very excellent manner.  People are
appreciating that the
company has launched an amazing product in which
unlimited sum assured is given, unlimited
ration is given, unlimited no claim bonus is
given and AB CD option is given,
any chronic disease is covered within 30 days,
BP, sugar, asthma
is covered only after 30 days, you will not get such unique feature in
any other company in the market, the
premium
is reasonable, the company
provides excellent handling, 100% digital platform, the
company provides
world class knowledge training of excellent level,
joining which is very simple,
for which the list of documents is
given on the side, you have to share this list of documents
with us,
after giving these documents I will have a virtual interaction with you,
after the interaction you will have to give an exam and the
exam fee is ₹1,
you get this working only after passing the exam, you get a
license in which you can work life long,
but before taking the license,
two  There are also mandatory conditions which
you have to fulfill. After getting the number one code, it is
mandatory to do 12 policies for one policy of ₹1500000. It is very important for health
insurance
that I am talking only about health here, so it is
mandatory to do the first policy of health and 12 policies of health in 1 year. You can do more than this as much as you want
and you have to make two basic commitments
with us because I am from Delhi,
you can be from anywhere from UP to Bihar to Maharashtra to Assam to
Bengal, you can be from
anywhere in all over India.
More than 1000 agents are
working with us all over India, you can also be one of them. It is a
completely digital platform, there is
no need to go to any branch,
we provide all the knowledge training
through Zoom meetings and
apart from this, you will also get five-seven trainings from my side
which can be valuable for you.
Friends, it only costs ₹1 for a one-
time exam,
apart from this, you have to do it for life.  You do not have to pay any money
and if we talk about your earning here, then let me make it
clear that you do
not get any kind of salary here, you
get only commission based income here, you will
get commission on whatever number of policies you sell,
you can earn commission from 15% to 35% here, plus you
get domestic trips here,
plus you get international trips, there are
quarterly contests, there are yearly clubs
which you can easily achieve
and we will
generally provide you all the knowledge training in the training,
those who want to join us on all over India basis
with this wonderful company,
then
you will have to do health only through WhatsApp-web first, only
after that we support for motor and non-motor
because we are
from health vertical, I hope
you have understood the content, Hello your friend
Yogendra Verma, thank you so much